export default cards = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "Name the String methods that work with RegEx patterns:",
        correct_answer: "match",
        answer1: "replace",
        answer2: "search",
        answer3: "split"
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "what are the RegEx flags supported by js?",
        correct_answer: "g for global",
        answer1: "i for ignore case",
        answer2: "m for multiline",
        answer: "none"
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "Name the greatest human of all time:",
        correct_answer: "Guido van Rossum",
        answer1: "Richard Stallman",
        answer2: "Bram Moolenaar",
        answer: "James Gosling"
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "What Is Pi?",
        correct_answer: "=~3.1415926535…",
        answer1: "Pi is a type of dish",
        answer2: "Pi is unknown",
        answer: "Pi is a constant"
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "What's 8 * 3",
        correct_answer: "24",
        answer1: "17",
        answer2: "20",
        answer: "19"
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "What's (a + b)^2",
        correct_answer: "a^2 + 2ab + b^2",
        answer1: "a^2 – 2ab + b^2",
        answer2: "a^2 - b^2",
        answer: "indentities"
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "What programmation language is used the most?",
        correct_answer: "Python",
        answer1: "Ruby",
        answer2: "JavaScript",
        answer: "Java"
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "what cryptocurrency is used the most?",
        correct_answer: "Litecoin (LTC)",
        answer1: "Ethereum (ETH)",
        answer2: "Zcash (ZEC)",
        answer: "Dash (DASH)"
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "Which Linux command is used to rename a file?",
        correct_answer: "mv",
        answer1: "ls",
        answer2: "ps",
        answer: "rn"
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "Who is Bram Moolenaar?",
        correct_answer: "Creator of vim",
        answer1: "God",
        answer2: "Creator of Python",
        answer: "Dutch man"
    },
]